<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beyond the Corner Office</title>
    <description>A Jonathan Gardner Blog</description>
    <link>http://0.0.0.0:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Bash Profile</title>
        <description>
          
          I have been using a MacBook Pro as my primary work computer for about 6 months now. As a developer, photographer, and video editor I have have always been partial to them in my personal life. I have been spending more and more time in the Terminal app then ever...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2017-08-22-Bash-Profile/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/2017-08-22-Bash-Profile/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inspire Presentation - Bots and AI</title>
        <description>
          
          This week I had a chance to lead a small group discussion on Bots and Artificial intelligence at the Microsoft Inspire Partner Conference. Some people were interested in my slides so I have included a link to the slides here. During that discussion, we covered an overview of Bots and...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2017-07-11-Inspire-Presentation/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/2017-07-11-Inspire-Presentation/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Blog, New Role</title>
        <description>
          
          A new blog and a new role here at Microsoft. Starting today I am joining the Azure Customer Advisory Team. I am excited for the challenge and look forward to learning from wealth of experience hard won working on some of the most challenging and innovative customer solutions. I hope...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 05:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2017-06-03-new-role-new-blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/2017-06-03-new-role-new-blog/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Advanced Azure ARM Template</title>
        <description>
          
          As you have seen, I have been doing quite a bit of work with ARM templates and VMs recently. This post is no different. I have been working on a project where multiple VMs need to be created from a custom image and they need to be joined to an...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2016-07-22-Advanced-VM-ARM-Template/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/2016-07-22-Advanced-VM-ARM-Template/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Azure Resource Manager Template Custom Script Extensions</title>
        <description>
          
          In my previous article, Building Azure Resource Manager Templates , I covered how to get started with Azure Resource Manager templates. While they are certainly great for basic deployments, where they really shine is in their ability to allow for complex deployments. This post will cover the Custom Script Extension...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2016-04-26-Azure-Resource-Manager-Templates-Custom-Script-Extensions/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/2016-04-26-Azure-Resource-Manager-Templates-Custom-Script-Extensions/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shutdown Tagged VMs with Azure Automation</title>
        <description>
          
          In my previous post PowerShell to update the tags on resources, I added tags to the virtual machines in my subscription. There are a host of reasons why resources may be tagged in Azure. I have seen customers use them to identify the department or application resources belong to. I...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2016-04-21-Shutdown-Tagged-VMs-with-Azure-Automation/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/2016-04-21-Shutdown-Tagged-VMs-with-Azure-Automation/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Adding Tags to Resources in Azure</title>
        <description>
          
          I am always looking for ways to automate my Azure environment. I use Azure as a Demo and Testing environment and do not want it running 24/7 and shutting off each virtual machine at the end of a day is time consuming. I want to have Azure Automation do that...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2016-04-12-Adding-Tags-to-Resources-in-Azure/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/2016-04-12-Adding-Tags-to-Resources-in-Azure/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Azure Automation, My SQL Agent in the Cloud</title>
        <description>
          
          My focus for the past 18 moths at Microsoft has been on Azure but that does not mean I left my love for SQL behind. In fact, has become an asset. In the course of regular operations I have built out a workflow to import call statistics and reporting data...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2016-04-12-azure-automation-sql/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/2016-04-12-azure-automation-sql/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
